{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Dryer Vent Cleaning Services","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46423/":{"taskOID":46423,"originalTaskOID":46423,"setID":1415,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6938,"questionDisplayText":"Type of system","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of system needs cleaning?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Dryer vent","answerDisplayText":"Dryer vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10147,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Heating or cooling air ducts","answerDisplayText":"Heating or cooling air ducts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10148,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both air ducts \u0026 dryer vent","answerDisplayText":"Both air ducts \u0026 dryer vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6939,"questionDisplayText":"Number of vents","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many registers/vents need cleaning?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10150,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10151,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5","answerDisplayText":"2-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10152,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-10","answerDisplayText":"6-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10153,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11-15","answerDisplayText":"11-15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10154,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 15","answerDisplayText":"More than 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4695,"questionDisplayText":"System Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the system located?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1450,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Closet","answerDisplayText":"Closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4483,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4696,"questionDisplayText":"Want Disinfectant Fog","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you want a disinfectant fog (to eliminate mold, bacteria, and dust mites)?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6938,"questionDisplayText":"Type of system","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of system needs cleaning?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Dryer vent","answerDisplayText":"Dryer vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10147,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Heating or cooling air ducts","answerDisplayText":"Heating or cooling air ducts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10148,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both air ducts \u0026 dryer vent","answerDisplayText":"Both air ducts \u0026 dryer vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Dryer vent","answerDisplayText":"Dryer vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10147,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Heating or cooling air ducts","answerDisplayText":"Heating or cooling air ducts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10148,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both air ducts \u0026 dryer vent","answerDisplayText":"Both air ducts \u0026 dryer vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6939,"questionDisplayText":"Number of vents","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many registers/vents need cleaning?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10150,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10151,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5","answerDisplayText":"2-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10152,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-10","answerDisplayText":"6-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10153,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11-15","answerDisplayText":"11-15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10154,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 15","answerDisplayText":"More than 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10150,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10151,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2-5","answerDisplayText":"2-5","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10152,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-10","answerDisplayText":"6-10","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10153,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"11-15","answerDisplayText":"11-15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10154,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 15","answerDisplayText":"More than 15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4695,"questionDisplayText":"System Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the system located?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1450,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Closet","answerDisplayText":"Closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4483,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":881,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Attic","answerDisplayText":"Attic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1450,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Closet","answerDisplayText":"Closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5389,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Roof","answerDisplayText":"Roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4483,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4696,"questionDisplayText":"Want Disinfectant Fog","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you want a disinfectant fog (to eliminate mold, bacteria, and dust mites)?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/46423/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46423,"taskName":"Dryer Vents - Clean","taskDescription":"Clean Dryer Vent","xmTaskDescriptor":"Dryer Vent Cleaning Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1004,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"vent, dryer, clean","textMessagingName":"Dryer Vent","rolloverLongDesc":"Involves running a device through the Dryer Vent to dislodge dust, dirt \u0026 mold so that it can be collected by a large, often truck-mounted, vacuum cleaner.","rolloverShortDesc":"Clean Dryer vents","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Clean a Dryer Vent.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Clean Dryer Vents \u003cin_city\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Dryer Vent Cleaning","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":13,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Clean Dryer Vent","redirectToTaskOid":40183,"spDisplayName":"Dryer Vent - Clean","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Dryer Vent Cleaning Project","urlName":"Dryer-Vent-Clean","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"Dryer Vent Cleaning \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Clean Dryer Vent","searchKeywords":"dryer,clean,vent,cleaner,cleaning,Ducts,Duct,Vents,Vent, lint","emcCategoryOid":-12014,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1415,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}